

NICHOLAS MENDEZ

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER || FRONT-END DEVELOPER

SKILLS

- HTML, CSS JavaScript
- React Js | React Native
- C# | Java | Kotlin | Dart
- Flutter/Jetpack Compose
- Node JS
- Zoho (crm, deluge, creator)
- Python
- PostgresSQL
- MySQL
- JIRA / Atlassian API
- Android | Studio
- Twilio

EDUCATION

Brigham Young University-Pathway Worldwide

Applied Technology

2021- present.

Universidad Dominicana O&M System engineering 2018- 2020

Tecnico profesional en informatica

Instituto politecnico cardenal Sancha

2011-2015

CONTACT

- Santo Domingo, Republica Dominicana
- nicholasmeeendez@gmail.com
- +1809-873-6034
- Nicholas Gabriel Mendez
 Bertrand
 www.linkedin.com/in/NicholasG
 Mendez
- NicholasMendez11 https://github.com/NicholasMendez11

ABOUT ME

2 years of experience. Creating systems to address business needs. Focussed on building web applications, cross-mobile applications with React Native, Android native apps with jetpack Compose, and developing integrations for Zoho's CRM and BPM.

Learner by passion

WORK EXPERIENCE

IDT Corporation, Software developer

MARCH 2022 - PRESENT

 Providing support to the internal departments of the company in the optimization, development, and implementation of new technologies. Working directly with Zoho ecosystems and other data support tools.

Scotia GBS., Workforce Analyst

MAY 2021 - MARCH 2022

 interpret, analyze and optimize data. Make recommendations that improve a workforce with an eye on reducing overhead and increasing customer satisfaction and experience/

Continuum, Tech Support

MAY 2019 - OCTUBER 2019

- Provide with technical solutions and broadband assistance to a huge variety of customers of Windstream Communications.
- Monitoring customer's quality connection, performing quality tests and pings to their routers in order to determinate how their problems could be resolved.

PORTAFOLIO

https://portafolio-one-zeta.vercel.app/